I think I need to chip in a word, before we go for healing.
Healing, deliverance and all of God's blessings
are hindered by the way and manner we go about the issue of money.
I will repeat again
Healing, deliverance and all of Gods blessings
are hindered today,
by the way and manner we go about the issue of money,money,money.
No one can give money from his heart before healing.
Anybody that gives money before healing is giving that money on condition,
Heal me- have money.
Healing and Gods blessing should not be exchanged with money.
When we give freely,
as we have been given freely
God will raise his people to bless us-
abundantly
Anything that does not come to the heart is a sin
If someone gives money before healing,
He has not given it from his heart, he has given it to receive healing.
And anything that is not from the heart, is a sin.
This is why it is so difficult to receive healing and deliverance today.
All these- Gods blessings, are hindered
by the manner and way we go about money.
Thank you!
Whatever you give me now, before prayer, is not from your heart.
Whatever you give me now, before your healing is not from your heart.
and anything that is not from the heart is a sin.
It means, you give me sin, tribulation, sickness -
You are giving me the affliction.
(The Spirit of God comes in the scene, as prophet T.B Joshua stretches forth his hand to pray for this lady.
Remember where the light of God is, darkness has no hiding place.
And healing, deliverance and all of God's blessing are just like breathing.)
I am very very sure, if I had collected money from her, she would not receive.
She is under the influence of the Holy Ghost
Rise and walk!
stand up!
(What a miracle, After receiving prayers from prophet T.B Joshua,
this lady begin to vomit out every poisonous substance from her body
which has been troubling her system for a very long time.)
(When Jesus comes into our lives he brushes away our past and gives birth to our glorious future)
(Glory be to God! she waves her hands is appreciation for the mighty miracle she has just received.)